Hi there my name is Luke and welcome to the course I'm going to be the teacher for this entire course.
大家好，我的名字是卢克，欢迎来到这门课程，我将成为整个课程的老师。
And I want to in this first video this introduction just basically introduce a few things about the
我想在第一个视频中，这个介绍基本上只是介绍一些关于
structure the style of the course as well as share a few tips things I'd like you to keep in mind things
构建课程的风格以及分享一些技巧我希望你记住的事情
I'd like you to remember throughout the course as you go through it.
我希望你在学习过程中记住整个课程。
Let's first just talk about the style of the course.
我们先来说说课程的风格。
Throughout this course for the entire course you're going to see me.
在整个课程中，您将看到我。
Going to see my head.
要去看看我的头。
See my face and see the blackboard.
看我的脸，看黑板。
I'll be writing on the blackboard throughout the course.
整个课程我都会在黑板上写字。
There will be no lessons in which you'll see the board or a screen and not me.
不会有任何课程让您看到黑板或屏幕，而不是我。
There'll be no lessons in which you see me and not the board.
不会有你看到我而不是董事会的课程。
We'll always be together me and my me and my best friend the blackboard.
我们将永远在一起我和我的我和我最好的朋友黑板。
That's a heart that's bad.
那是一颗坏的心。
Speaking of a bad heart there will be times when my writing will be beat.
说到心脏不好，有时我的写作会被打败。
Maybe a little bit just a little bit messy because I'm writing quickly.
也许有点乱，因为我写得很快。
I think you will get used to how I write over time so if you find it difficult in the first or second
我想随着时间的推移你会习惯我的写作方式，所以如果你在第一秒或第二秒觉得很难
lesson to understand what I'm writing sometimes I think it'll get better.
了解我在写什么的教训有时我认为它会变得更好。
After a couple more lessons because you have to get used to someone's writing style to be able to easily
再上几节课后，因为您必须习惯某人的写作风格才能轻松
read it and if I write very slowly then it will be extremely boring.
阅读它，如果我写得很慢，那将非常无聊。
Right.
正确的。
OK.
好的。
Next let's talk about what we're going to learn in this course.
接下来让我们谈谈我们将在本课程中学习的内容。
Well you can read through all of the lessons in the course and see what the contents are.
那么你可以通读课程中的所有课程，看看内容是什么。
But I want to just say something about how I've decided to structure it.
但我只想谈谈我决定如何构建它。
That means how I've decided to organize it.
这意味着我决定如何组织它。
I've said before I've been working on this course for a very very long time years and I've organized
我之前说过，我已经在这门课程上工作了很长时间，并且我已经组织了
the lessons in this course so that it's number one building upon things we learned previously that means
本课程中的课程，因此它是建立在我们之前学到的东西之上的第一，这意味着
we learn something and then later on we'll use it.
我们学到了一些东西，然后我们会使用它。
For example will learn about descriptions early in the course and then use those skills later on but
例如，将在课程的早期学习描述，然后在以后使用这些技能，但是
also to keep it interesting.
也是为了保持有趣。
So we might do something social kind of fun like a situation that you'll encounter in daily life.
所以我们可能会做一些有趣的社交活动，比如你会在日常生活中遇到的情况。
Lots of those and then we'll have something a little more technical such as a particular English skill
很多，然后我们会有一些更技术性的东西，比如特定的英语技能
that you need to do a particular thing and then maybe the next one will be a little bit more fun.
你需要做一件特定的事情，然后也许下一件事情会更有趣。
And by doing that and having that variety I hope that the course will continue to be interesting and
通过这样做并拥有这样的多样性，我希望这门课程将继续有趣和
continue to stay fresh.
继续保持新鲜。
There will certainly be a couple of times when maybe a particular thing that we're learning is a bit
肯定会有几次我们正在学习的特定事物有点
a bit dry.
有点干。
I try my best not to make it boring dry means boring although those skills are very important.
我尽力不让它变得无聊枯燥意味着无聊，尽管这些技能非常重要。
Everything I've put into this course is important for people who want to improve their English.
我在这门课程中所做的一切对于想要提高英语的人来说都很重要。
If you're working on your spoken English even your written English this course will help you and everything
如果您正在学习口语，甚至是书面英语，本课程将对您和一切都有帮助
in this course is meant to be useful in your real life.
本课程旨在对您的现实生活有用。
Just one more thing I want to mention before we talk about what to keep in mind throughout the course
在我们讨论整个课程中要记住的内容之前，我还想提一件事
and that is that I've broken lessons down into smaller parts.
那就是我把课程分解成更小的部分。
If you have a long video that's 45 minutes long.
如果您有一个 45 分钟长的长视频。
It can be quite difficult to go through that whole thing.
经历整个事情可能非常困难。
Right.
正确的。
It can be something that you might think about for a whole week.
这可能是您可能会考虑一整周的事情。
Oh I have to do this 45 minute video right.
哦，我必须做这个 45 分钟的视频。
It's like it's like needing to run up a big hill but if it's smaller if it's 10 minutes it's easier
这就像它需要跑一个大嗨ll 但是如果它更小，如果它是 10 分钟，那就更容易了
to digest the Hill is a little smaller.
消化山就小了一点。
So even though it's part of a larger lesson each piece is easier to eat.
所以即使它是一个更大的课程的一部分，每一块都更容易吃。
Each Hill is smaller.
每座山都较小。
So that's why I've done that.
所以这就是我这样做的原因。
The lessons are broken up into smaller pieces.
课程被分成更小的部分。
Now things I'd like you to keep in mind throughout the course keep in mind means things to remember
现在我希望你在整个课程中记住的事情记住意味着要记住的事情
throughout the course.
在整个课程中。
Number one it's very important that you take notes.
第一，做笔记非常重要。
If you're sitting down at your computer if you're using your phone whatever.
如果你坐在电脑前，如果你正在使用手机，无论如何。
Take notes.
做笔记。
If you take notes on your computer that's fine.
如果你在电脑上做笔记就好了。
You want to take notes on a piece of paper or in a notebook.
您想在一张纸或笔记本上做笔记。
That's fine.
没关系。
I don't care but you want to take notes so that you're doing some action connected to what you're learning.
我不在乎，但你想记笔记，这样你就可以做一些与你所学内容相关的行动。
If you're only listening it may be hard to remember the things that you're learning.
如果你只是在听，可能很难记住你正在学习的东西。
But if you have some action you're putting the things that you're learning into the real world.
但如果你有一些行动，你就是将你正在学习的东西放到现实世界中。
And by doing that the things that you're learning are going to stick more next.
通过这样做，您正在学习的东西接下来会更加坚持。
Don't hurry through this course if you rush through this course and try to finish it in several days.
如果您匆忙完成这门课程并尝试在几天内完成它，请不要急于完成这门课程。
I think that you'll probably miss a lot of stuff unless you're a super genius and great at remembering
我认为你可能会错过很多东西，除非你是一个超级天才并且善于记忆
every little thing you hear.
你听到的每一件小事。
I recommend that you take your time watch one video a day or one video every two days.
我建议您花时间每天看一个视频或每两天看一个视频。
That's OK.
没关系。
Don't rush through the course.
不要急于完成课程。
When you take your time you allow yourself time to practice what you've learned to review your notes
当你慢慢来时，你会让自己有时间练习你所学的东西来复习你的笔记
and to just think about what you heard in the previous lesson.
想想你在上一节课中听到的内容。
That time to think is as important as actually learning the stuff right.
思考的时间与实际学习正确的东西一样重要。
When you become a painter you paint and then you think oh I don't like this.
当你成为一名画家时，你会画画，然后你会想，哦，我不喜欢这样。
I could be better you go away.
我最好你走开。
You think about what you did and what you could do better.
你想想你做了什么，你可以做得更好。
You come back and then you paint better the next time.
你回来，然后你下次画得更好。
Well that's true for a lot of things and it's true for learning as well.
嗯，很多事情都是如此，学习也是如此。
So I recommend that you have some space between each video so that you have time to review you have
所以我建议你在每个视频之间留出一些空间，这样你就有时间回顾你有
time to practice and you have time to reflect to reflect means to think walk around look at the clouds.
有时间练习，你有时间反思反思意味着思考走动看看云。
Have a cup of coffee whatever you need to do.
喝杯咖啡，无论你需要做什么。
OK.
好的。
Very important as well.
也非常重要。
Next you need to review.
接下来你需要复习。
You've got a review with each lesson there's something you can practice.
每节课你都有一个复习，你可以练习一些东西。
And I've attached basically an assignment to each lesson.
我基本上为每节课附上了一个作业。
What you can do to practice what you've learned.
你可以做什么来练习你所学的。
There's one really great way to practice English spoken English without actually talking with a friend.
有一种非常好的方法可以在不与朋友交谈的情况下练习英语口语。
Now it's great if you can great if you have a teacher that's great.
现在，如果您有一位很棒的老师，您可以很棒，那就太好了。
You have a friend you can talk with.
你有一个可以交谈的朋友。
That's wonderful.
那好极了。
But if you want to practice the stuff that you've learned in each lesson by itself by yourself.
但是，如果您想自己练习在每节课中学到的东西。
Turn on your phone open the recording app or whatever you want to use and record the practice that is
打开你的手机打开录音应用程序或任何你想使用并记录练习
sign.
符号。
So by recording yourself you're you're doing what I mentioned earlier when you're taking notes you are
因此，通过记录自己，您正在做我之前提到的做笔记时
putting something out there you're making something.
把东西放在那里你正在做一些东西。
Input output input output input an output go very well together.
输入输出输入输出输入输出配合得很好。
When it comes to learning and recording is a great way to do output output.
说到学习和记录，是一种很好的输出输出方式。
When it comes to learning languages when it comes to learning new spoken skills.
说到学习语言，当谈到学习新的口语技能时。
Then if you feel like you didn't really get something go back and review watch a lesson twice.
然后，如果您觉得自己并没有真正得到什么，请返回并复习两节课。
Watch a lesson three times if you need to when you finish this course go back and watch it again.
如果你需要看一课三遍，当你完成这门课后，再回去看一遍。
Whenever I read a book I usually read that book twice that way I make sure I don't miss anything right.
每当我读一本书时，我通常都会读两遍那本书，以确保我不会错过任何正确的东西。
If I went through it once I might have missed a couple of small things.
如果我经历过一次，我可能会错过一些小事情。
I go back I can catch those things that I might have missed the first time through.
我回去我可以抓住那些我第一次可能错过的东西。
I want to just mention one thing that's very important and something I would like you to keep in mind
我只想提一件非常重要的事情，我希望你牢记在心
as you go through this course and that is the importance of awareness as you're practicing what you
当你完成这门课程时，这就是在你练习你所学的时候意识的重要性
learn.
学。
It's very important to be able to pay attention to what you're saying.
能够注意你在说什么是非常重要的。
A lot of people when they're there speaking they don't pay attention to what sounds are coming out of
很多人在那里讲话时不会注意发出的声音
their own mouths.
他们自己的嘴。
Got to be able to pay attention to what you say.
必须能够注意你说的话。
So that recording exercise is a great way to do that because you're catching things that you wouldn't
所以记录练习是一个很好的方法，因为你正在捕捉你不会捕捉到的东西
normally catch but then you can start to do that for yourself when you're speaking and that allows you
通常会捕捉到，但是当你说话时你可以开始为自己做这件事，这样你就可以
to build better habits.
建立更好的习惯。
So I hope you can as you go through this course pay very careful attention to not only the sounds that
所以我希望你在学习这门课程时能够非常仔细地注意不仅仅是
I'm making right and the way that I'm saying what I'm saying but also when you're practicing what you're
我做对了，我说的方式是正确的，而且当你在练习时
saying and the sounds that you're making and how you're saying what you're saying it's very very important
说话和你发出的声音以及你说话的方式 你在说什么 这非常非常重要
so develop your awareness and that is the key to the next step which is building better habits building
所以培养你的意识，这是下一步建立更好习惯的关键
better habits is the key to ultimately becoming a more natural English speaker.
更好的习惯是最终成为更自然的英语演讲者的关键。
Finally before we get started on the first lesson of this course I'd like you to remember to keep an
最后，在我们开始这门课程的第一课之前，我希望你记得保持
open mind if there's something that you think is true about English maybe you learned that in school
敞开心扉，如果你认为关于英语的某些事情是正确的，也许你在学校学到了这一点
and it's not quite right.
这不太对。
So be open minded maybe maybe a way that you've learned is either incorrect or correct and not natural
所以要心胸开阔，也许你学到的一种方式要么不正确，要么正确，而且不自然
maybe native English speakers say something a different way even though that different way is not technically
也许以英语为母语的人会说一些不同的东西，即使这种不同的方式在技术上并不重要
correct.
正确的。
There are many examples of that in native spoken English and I will share some of those in this course.
以英语为母语的例子很多，我将在本课程中分享其中的一些。
OK.
好的。
So I'd like you to make a commitment to yourself to be open minded if you're close minded and you're
所以我希望你对自己做出一个开放的承诺，如果你思想封闭并且你是
always saying well that can't be right.
总是说好那是不对的。
That can't be right.
这不可能。
Then you're not going to learn as much.
那你就学不会那么多了。
So I encourage you to be more like a sponge a sponge absorbs things then the more you absorb you can
所以我鼓励你更像一块海绵海绵吸收东西然后你吸收的越多你就可以
begin to process it and you can start using it in your daily life.
开始处理它，您就可以开始在日常生活中使用它。
Learning English is all about ultimately really it's about learning to communicate with other people
学习英语最终是关于学习与他人交流
in writing or in conversation.
在书面或谈话中。
And that's the main point of this course to give you the skills and the knowledge that you need to go
这就是本课程的重点，为您提供所需的技能和知识
out into the world and use your language skills to communicate with people in a wide variety of situations.
走出去，用你的语言技能与各种情况下的人交流。
This course will help you in many different areas improve your skills improve your knowledge and improve
本课程将帮助您在许多不同的领域提高您的技能提高您的知识和提高
your ability to communicate in English with other people and without any more delay.
您用英语与他人交流的能力，不会再有任何延误。
Let's go to the actual first lesson of the course and I want to just say that I hope you enjoy it.
让我们进入课程的实际第一课，我只想说我希望你喜欢它。